

VELMURUGAN UI Developer

Contact

 \vee

velmuruganc6@gmail.com



Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India



https://www.linkedin.com/in/velmuruganc6



https://github.com/Velmuruganc6



https://velmurugan-ui.000webhostapp.com

Technical Skills

+91 9566102936

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

Javascript

JQuery

Bootstrap

Responsive Web Design

Website Performance

Angular

Angular Material

Rest API

Photoshop

Version Control(GIT & Bitbucket)

Languages

Tami

English

Professional Summary

Skilled and motivated UI Developer with 3.8 years of experience. Created 20+ websites advanced in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, and Front-end Frameworks. Received positive feedback's from management for punctuality, presentability and flexibility. Seeking a UI Developer position with a company which will require me to utilize my skill, abilities and experience in the IT field.

Experience

16th Dec 2020 - Present

UI Developer

Adding Smiles Pvt Ltd, Chennai

key Responsibilities

- Developed Front-end web pages with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, and Javascript.
- Resolved browsers compatibility issues, solving all conflicts for Firefox users.
- Creative responsive sites and flows that can be viewed on Mobile as well as Desktop.
- Responsive Web Design templates to meet cutting-edge technology requirements.
- Maintained front-end maintenance of websites.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.

Oct 2019 - 15th Dec 2020

UI Developer

FocuzAR Solutions Pvt Ltd, Chennai

key Responsibilities

- Developed Front-end web pages with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, and Javascript.
- Create Web Application using Angular Framework with Rest API.
- Resolved browsers compatibility issues, solving all conflicts for Firefox users.
- Creative responsive sites and flows that can be viewed on Mobile as well as Desktop.
- Creating reusable UI Components using Angular7.
- Creating Email template using HTML table layout conversion.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.

Jun 2018 - Sep 2019

UI Developer

Gharuda Infotech Pvt Ltd, Chennai

key Responsibilities

- Developed Front-end web pages with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, and Javascript.
- Resolved browsers compatibility issues, solving all conflicts for Firefox users.
- Creative responsive sites and flows that can be viewed on Mobile as well as Desktop.
- Responsive Web Design templates to meet cutting-edge technology requirements.
- Maintained front-end maintenance of websites.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.

Dec 2017 - May 2018

UI Developer

Pouzdan Technologies Pvt Ltd, Chennai

Education

2013 - 2017 B.E (CSE)

New Prince Shri Bhavani College of Engineering & Technology, Chennai

2012 - 2103 HSG

Christ The King Matriculation Higher

Secondary School, Chennai

2010 - 2011 SSLC

Zigma Matriculation Higher Secondary

School, Chennai